Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm 5752 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Examiners' Reports continued; Findings and Awards (Reel 4)
  - Brushmakers, Local 35 v. Chicago Brush Manufacturing. Chicago., 13 (Reel 4)
  - H.J. Zeller et al. v. American Wood Rim. Onaway, MI., 14 (Reel 4)
  - Molders, Local 5 v. Pero Foundry et al. Worcester, MA., 15 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Columbia Metal Box. New York City., 16 (Reel 4)
  - Teamsters, Local 42 v. Coal Dealers. Lynn, MA., 17 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Kokomo Spring. Kokomo, IN., 18 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. R.R. Donnelly and Sons. Chicago, IL., 19 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. John Bath. Worcester, MA., 20 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Standard Plunger Elevator. Worcester, MA., 21 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Industrial Manufacturing. Camden, NJ., 22 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Savage Arms. Utica, NY., 23 (Reel 4)
  - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 267 v. Wharton Steel. Wharton, NJ., 24 (Reel 4)
  - Wire and Rope Mill Workers, Union 16295 v. Williamsport Wire Rope. Williamsport, PA., 25 (Reel 4)
  - Molders, Local 205 v. Simpson Foundry. Newark, OH., 26 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Becker Milling Machine. Hyde Park, MA., 27 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists v. Wellman-Seaver-Morgan. South Akron, OH., 28 (Reel 4)
  - Textile Workers v. International Braid. Providence, RI., 29 (Reel 4)
  - Leather Workers v. Roundtree Trunk and Bag. Richmond, VA., 30 (Reel 4)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen v. Retail Grocers and Butchers. East St. Louis, IL., 31 (Reel 4)
  - Federal Labor Union 10875 v. Crown Cork and Seal. Baltimore, MD., 32 (Reel 4)
  - Molders, Local 318 v. Parsons Foundry. Newton, IA., 33 (Reel 4)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers, Local 78 v. Bryden Horse Shoe. Catasauqua, PA., 34 (Reel 4)
  - Buffers and Setters v. Alexander Brothers. Philadelphia., 35 (Reel 4)
  - Metal Trades Council v. Baker Iron Works. Los Angeles., 36 (Reel 4)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers, Local 7 v. Llewellyn Iron Works. Torrance, CA., 37 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electrical Railway Employees v. Public Service Railway. Newark, NJ., 38 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Remington Arms et al. Hoboken, NJ., 39 (Reel 4)
  - Window Glass Workers v. Vim Motor. Sandusky, OH., 40 (Reel 4)
  - Iron Workers, Local 240 v. Lehigh Structural Steel. Allentown, PA., 41 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Sexauer and Lemke. Long Island City, NY., 42 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists v. Armstrong Cork. Lancaster, PA., 43 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists v. Bearings. Lancaster, PA., 44 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists v. Champion Blower and Forge. Lancaster, PA., 45 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists v. Barry and Zecher. Lancaster, PA., 46 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists v. D.H. Potts. Lancaster, PA., 47 (Reel 4)
  - American Federation of Labor et al. v. Otis Steel. Cleveland, OH., 48 (Reel 4)
  - Printing Pressmen's Local 17 v. Indianapolis Publishers' Association. Indianapolis., 49 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Budd and Ranney Engineering. Columbus, OH., 50 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Superior Tool Die and Machine. Columbus, OH., 51 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Ralston Steel Car. Columbus, OH., 52 (Reel 4)
  - Photo-Engravers' Local 1 v. Publishers Association of New York. New York City., 53 (Reel 4)
  - Molders and Core Makers v. Barlow Foundry et al. Newark, NJ., 54 (Reel 4)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers, Local 99 v. Carpenter Steel. Reading, PA., 55 (Reel 4)
  - Federal Labor Union 15047 v. Northwestern Leather. Sault Ste. Marie, MI, 56 (Reel 4)
    .1 p.
  - Molders and Coremakers v. Worthington Pump and Machinery. Harrison, NJ., 57 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. J.C. Hearn Machine. Columbus, OH., 58 (Reel 4)
  - Locomotive Crane Engineers v. Seaboard By-Product Coke. Jersey City, NJ, 59 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Standard Pattern Works. Cincinnati, OH., 60 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Rome Manufacturing et al. Rome, NY., 61 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Rockport Granite. Rockport, MA., 62 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Rome Locomotive. Rome, NY, 63 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Rome Wire. Rome, NY., 64 (Reel 4)
  - Molders, Local 397 v. Ann Arbor Machine et al. Ann Arbor, MI., 65 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Westfield Manufacturing. Westfield, MA., 66 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists, Local 241 v. Hooven, Owens, and Rentschler. Hamilton, OH., 67 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Standard Conveyer. North St. Paul, MN., 68 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Blackmer Post Pipe et al. St. Louis, MO., 69 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Tennessee Copper. Copper Hill, TN., 70 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists v. Toledo Bridge and Crane et al. Toledo, OH., 71 (Reel 4)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 137 v. Municipal Gas. Albany, NY., 72 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Western Chemical. Denver., 73 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Citizens Ice et al. Los Angeles., 74 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Louisville Gas and Electric. Louisville, KY., 75 (Reel 4)
  - Composition Roofers, Local 32 v. Master Slag and Composition Roofers. Philadelphia, 76 (Reel 4)
  - Box Makers and Sawyers, Local 1 v. Acme Box et al. Chicago., 77 (Reel 4)
  - Silk Manufacturers v. Textile Workers. Paterson, NJ., 78 (Reel 4)
  - Marine Firemen, Water Tenders and Oilers v. East Coast Fisheries et al. Boston., 79 (Reel 4)
  - Masters, Mates and Pilots v. East Coast Fisheries et al. Boston., 80 (Reel 4)
  - Fish Handlers v. East Coast Fisheries et al. Boston., 81 (Reel 4)
  - Checklist of Awards and Findings., 82 (Reel 4)
  - Commercial Telegraphers et al. v. Western Union et al. New York City, 83 (Reel 4)
  - Industrial Workers et al. v. Employers Association et al. St. Louis, MO., 84 (Reel 4)
  - Marine Workers Affiliation v. Boat Owners. New York City., 85 (Reel 4)
  - Marine Workers Affiliation v. Boat Owners. New York City., 86 (Reel 4)
  - Miners, Local 261 v. Sloss-Sheffield Steel and Iron. Russellville, AL., 87 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Worthington Pump and Machinery. East Cambridge MA., 88 (Reel 4)
  - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 226 v. St. Joseph Lead. Herculaneum, MO., 89 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. General Electric. Pittsfield, MA., 90 (Reel 4)
  - Cranemen v. General Electric. Schenectady, NY., 91 (Reel 4)
  - Federal Labor Union 15543 et al. v. Hammond Lumber et al. Van Buren, ME., 92 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists et al. v. Bethlehem Steel. Bethlehem, PA., 93 (Reel 4)
  - Steam Engineers, Local 45 et al. v. Joplin and Pittsburg Railway. Joplin, MO, and Pittsburg, KS., 94 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland Railway. Cleveland, OH., 95 (Reel 4)
    1o pp.
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 26 v. Detroit United Railway. Detroit., 96 (Reel 4)
  - Papermakers v. International Paper et al. New York City., 97 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists, Local 818 et al. v. Wheeling Mold and Foundry et al. Wheeling, WV., 98 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists et al. v. Frick Company et al. Waynesboro, PA., 99 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 168 v. Scranton Railway. Scranton, PA., 100 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 125 et al. v. East St. Loius and Suburban Railway et al. East St. Louis, IL., 101 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 576 v. Schenectady Railway. Schenectady, NY., 102 (Reel 4)
  - Electrical Workers v. Northern Indiana Gas and Electric. Hammond, IN., 103 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists, Local 46 v. Minneapolis Steel and Machinery et al. Minneapolis, MN., 104 (Reel 4)
  - Certain Employees and Labor Unions v. Certain Employers in Minneapolis, St. Paul, and Vicinity., 105 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Virginia Bridge and Iron. Roanoke, VA., 106 (Reel 4)
  - Stove Mounters, Local 8 v. Estate Stove. Hamilton, OH., 107 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 380 v. Cleveland, Southwestern and Columbus Railway. Cleveland, OH., 108 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 241 and 308 v. Chicago Surface Lines et al. Chicago., 109 (Reel 4)
  - Coopers, Local 193 v. Wooden Tank Manufacturers. Chicago., 110 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. American Locomotive. Schenectady, NY., 111 (Reel 4)
  - Painters Union 47 et al. v. Master House Painters et al. Indianapolis., 112 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Public Service Railway. Newark, NJ., 113 (Reel 4)
  - Portland Railway, Light and Power v. Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 757. Portland, OR., 114 (Reel 4)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen v. Western Cold Storage. Chicago., 115 (Reel 4)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 566 v. Wilson Provision et al. Peoria, IL., 116 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 735 v. Jacksonville Traction. Jacksonville, FL., 117 (Reel 4)
  - Chicago Foundrymen's Association v. International Molders' Union of North America. Chicago., 118 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 802 v. Kansas City and Western railway. Leavenworth, KS., 119 (Reel 4)
  - Iron, Steel and Tin Workers v. Southern California Iron and Steel. Los Angeles., 120 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Willys-Overland. Elyria OH., 121 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 132 and 148 v. United Traction. Albany, NY., 122 (Reel 4)
  - Boilermakers v. National Refining. Coffeyville, KS., 123 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 194 v. New Orleans Railway and Light. New Orleans., 124 (Reel 4)
  - Blacksmiths and Helpers v. Pollak Steel. Cincinnati, OH., 125 (Reel 4)
  - Building Trades Employers Association v. Hod Carriers', Building, and Common Laborers' Union 10. Cleveland, OH., 126 (Reel 4)
  - Printing Pressmen's and Assistants' Local 4 v. Franklin Division of Franklin-Typothetae. Chicago., 127 (Reel 4)
  - Federal Labor Union 16104 v. Emerson Brantingham Manufacturing et al. Batavia, IL., 128 (Reel 4)
  - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 266 v. Trenton Smelter and Refining. Trenton, NJ., 129 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 515 v. Galesburg Railway, Lightning, and Power. Galesburg, IL., 130 (Reel 4)
  - Employees v. Red Star Milling et al. Wichita, KS., 131 (Reel 4)
  - Machinists, Local 64 v. Mason Machine Works. Taunton, MA., 132 (Reel 4)
  - Molder, Local 244 v. Central Specialty et al. Detroit., 133 (Reel 4)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 282, 580, and 532 v. New York State Railways. Rochester, NY., 134 (Reel 4)
- Findings and Awards continued (Reel 5)
  - Machinists, Local 330 v. Russell Motor Car. Buffalo, NY., 1 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. General Electric. Schenectady, NY., 2 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists, Local 1 v. Midvale Steel and Ordnance. Philadelphia., 3 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Corn Products Refining Company. Granite City, FL., 4 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Pennsylvania-New Jersey Railway. Trenton, NJ., 5 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists, local 30, 782, and 826 v. Employers. Bridgeport, CT., 6 (Reel 5)
  - Electric Linemen, Local 30 v. Erie Lighting Company et al. Erie, PA., 7 (Reel 5)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. A.M. Byers. Girard, OH., 8 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 817 et al. v. Columbus Railway, Power, and Light. Columbus, OH., 9 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. Jackson and Church et al. Saginaw, MI., 10 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 806, 810, 749 v. City Railway et al. Dayton, OH., 11 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 623 v. International Railway. Buffalo, NY., 12 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 807 v. Omaha and Council Bluffs Street Railway. Omaha, NE., 13 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 196 v. United Foundry and Engineering. Youngstown, OH., 14 (Reel 5)
  - Pattern Makers v. Triangle Pattern and Manufacturing et al. Detroit., 15 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 732 v. Georgia Railway and Power. Atlanta., 16 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 81 v. A.F. Brown et al. Elizabethtown, NJ., 17 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. Worthington Pump and Machinery. Cudahy, WI., 18 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland and Eastern Traction. Cleveland, OH., 19 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Middletown Car. Middletown, PA., 20 (Reel 5)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers et al. v. National Enameling and Stamping. Granite City, IL and St. Louis, MO., 21 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 746 v. Denver City Tramway. Denver., 22 (Reel 5)
  - Federal Labor Union 15047 v. Union Carbide. Sault Ste. Marie, MI., 23 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 805 v. East St. Louis, Columbia, and Waterloo Railway. East St. Louis, IL., 24 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Standard Wheel. Terre Haute, IN., 25 (Reel 5)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 601 v. Hammond Packing et al. Pittsburgh and McKeesport, PA., 26 (Reel 5)
  - Metal Trades Council v. Ajax Iron Works et al. Denver., 27 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 618 v. Rhode Island Company. Providence, RI., 28 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 589 v. Boston Elevated Railway. Boston., 29 (Reel 5)
  - Leather Workers v. National Leather Belting et al. New York City., 30 (Reel 5)
  - Providence Central Federated Union v. Rhode Island Branch, National Metal Trades Association. Providence, RI., 31 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland, Painesville, and Eastern Railroad et al. Cleveland, OH., 32 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists et al. v. Employers. Madison, WI., 33 (Reel 5)
    22 pp.
  - Machinists, Local 46 et al. v. Minneapolis Steel and Machinery et al. Minneapolis, MN., 34 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 761 v. Springfield Consolidated. Springfield Consolidated. Springfield, IL., 35 (Reel 5)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 524 and 165 v. North Western Fuel et al. Superior, WI., 36 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 669 v. Auburn and Syracuse Electric Railroad. Auburn, NY., 37 (Reel 5)
  - Pattern makers v. Metal Trades Employers. Birmingham, AL, 38 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 713 v. Memphis Street Railway. Memphis, TN., 39 (Reel 5)
  - Conductors, Trainmen, and Engineers v. Interurban Lines. Portland, OR., 40 (Reel 5)
  - Stove Mounters, Local 1 v. Michigan Stove et al. Detroit, MI, 41 (Reel 5)
  - Railroad Trainmen, Lodge 808 et al. v. Pacific Electric Railway. Los Angeles., 42 (Reel 5)
  - Carpenters, Local 14 et al. v. Thomas Harmon et al. San Antonio., 43 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists, Local 161 v. Kleiber-Dawson Machine. Indianapolis., 44 (Reel 5)
  - Firefighters v. Municipal Government. Pittsburgh, PA., 45 (Reel 5)
  - Hardwood Finishers, Local 426 et al. v. Manufacturers of Interior Woodwork. Philadelphia., 46 (Reel 5)
  - Lynn Central Labor Union et al. v. General Electric. Lynn, MA., 47 (Reel 5)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. American Sheet and Tin Plate. Elwood, IN., 48 (Reel 5)
  - Laundry Workers, Local 36 v. Imperial Laundry et al. Little Rock, AR., 49 (Reel 5)
  - Meat Cutters v. Brockton Shoe manufacturers. Brockton, MA., 50 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists, Local 335 v. Connersville Blower et al. Connersville, IN., 51 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 737 v. Northern Electric Railway. Syracuse, NY., 52 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. Linderman Steel and Machinery. Muskegon, MI., 53 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 767 v. Knoxville Railway and Light. Knoxville, TN., 54 (Reel 5)
  - Mechanics v. Steel Ship Link Belt. Chicago, 55 (Reel 5)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, Local 386 et al. v. St. Louis Coffin. St. Louis, MO., 56 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Atlantic Elevator et al. Minneapolis, MN., 57 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 764 v. Kansas City Railways. Kansas City, MO., 58 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 199 v. Ottumwa Railway. Ottumwa, IA., 59 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 381 v. Butte Electric Railway. Butte, MT., 60 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. Smith and Wesson. Springfield, MA., 61 (Reel 5)
  - Federal Labor Union 16087 et al. v. Walworth Manufacturing. Kewanee, IL., 62 (Reel 5)
  - Textile Workers v. Lorraine Mills et al. Pawtucket, RI., 63 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 669 and 737 v. Rochester and Syracuse Railway. Syracuse, NY., 64 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 580 v. Syracuse and Suburban Railway. Syracuse, NY., 65 (Reel 5)
  - Locomotive Engineers, Local 419 and 868 v. New York Consolidated Railway. New York City., 66 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 62 v. Bass Foundry. Fort Wayne, IN., 67 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 681 and 737 v. Empire State Railroad. Syracuse, NY., 68 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. Hatcher Tool. Detroit, MI, 69 (Reel 5)
  - Steam Fitters, Local 572 et al. v. Nashville Munition Plant. Nashville, TN., 70 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 441 v. Des Moines City Railway. Des Moines, IA., 71 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 759 v. Lima Street Railway. Lima, OH., 72 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. New York Central Iron Works. Hagerstown, Maryland., 73 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 834 v. Columbus Street Railway. Columbus, GA., 74 (Reel 5)
  - Miners et al. v. Nevada Consolidated Copper. McGill, Ruth and Ely, NV., 75 (Reel 5)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. George W. Smith et al. Philadelphia., 76 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. A.H. Peterson Manufacturing. Milwaukee, Wi., 77 (Reel 5)
  - Elevator Operators and Starters, Local 495 v. Employers. San Francisco, 78 (Reel 5)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 227 v. Armour. Louisville, KY., 79 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Standard Boiler and Plate Iron. Niles, IA., 80 (Reel 5)
  - Workers v. National Car Coupler. Attica, IN., 81 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Third Avenue Railway. New York City., 82 (Reel 5)
  - Boilermakers, Local 127 v. Advance Rumley. Battle Creek, MI, 83 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Western Drop Forge. Marion, IN., 84 (Reel 5)
  - Foundry Employees, Local 66 et al. v. Baker Manufacturing. Saratoga Springs, NY., 85 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Pittsfield Machine and Tool. Pittsfield, MA., 86 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. American Locomotive Works. Paterson, NJ., 87 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. Niles-Bement-Pond. Plainfield, NJ., 88 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 312, 313, and 599 v. Tri-City Railway et al. Rock Island, IL., 89 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 752 v. Bloomington and Normal Railway. Bloomington, IL., 90 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 277 v. Niles-Bement-Pond et al. Ridgway, PA., 91 (Reel 5)
  - Molders v. Hyde Windlass. Bath, Maine., 92 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 183 v. Employers. Williamsport, PA., 93 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 70 et al. v. Foundrymen's Association. Boston, 94 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Detroit Forging. Detroit., 95 (Reel 5)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 343 v. Kern Mutual Telephone et al. Taft, CA., 96 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Wolf et al. Chambersburg, PA., 97 (Reel 5)
  - Employees of Distribution Department v. Public Service Gas. Camden, NJ, 98 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 420 v. Elkhart Iron Works et al. Elkhart, IN., 99 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Hoyte White Metal. Granite City, IL, 100 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. Sturtevant. Hyde Park, MA., 101 (Reel 5)
  - Coopers v. Sinclair Refining. Coffeyville, KS., 102 (Reel 5)
  - Blacksmiths v. Bedford Stone Club. Bedford, IN., 103 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists, Local 1 v. J.G. Brill et al. Philadelphia., 104 (Reel 5)
  - Discharged Employees v. Bethlehem Steel. North Lebanon, PA., 105 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 417 v. Baker Manufacturing et al. Saratoga Springs, NY., 106 (Reel 5)
  - Conductors and Motormen v. Michigan United Railways. Jackson, MI., 107 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati, Lawrenceburg, and Aurora Electric Railway. Cincinnati, OH., 108 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati Traction. Cincinnati, OH., 109 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati and Columbus Traction. Cincinnati, OH., 110 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 631 v. Cincinnati, Milford, and Loveland Traction. Cincinnati, OH., 111 (Reel 5)
  - Blacksmiths, Local 455 v. Evansville Tool Works. Evansville, IN, 112 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 831 v. Louisville Street Railway et al. Louisville, KY., 113 (Reel 5)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. Reading iron. Reading and Danville, PA., 114 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Eastern Steel. Pottsville, PA., 115 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Bethlehem Steel. North Lebanon, PA., 116 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Lebanon Valley Iron. Lebanon, PA., 117 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Burden Iron and Steel. Troy, NY, 118 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Cohoes Rolling Mill et al. Cohoes, NY., 119 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 714 v. Cumberland County Power and Light. Portland, ME., 120 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 395 v. Aetna Foundry et al. Warren, OH., 121 (Reel 5)
  - Labor v. Detroit Employers Association. Detroit, MI, 122 (Reel 5)
  - Electrical Workers v. Intermountain Power. Spokane, WA., 123 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Philadelphia Railways. Philadelphia., 124 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees v. Detroit United Railway. Detroit, MI., 125 (Reel 5)
  - Association of Employing Printers v. Printing Pressmen's and Assistants' Union, Local 23. New York City., 126 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 721 and 724 v. Lewiston, Augusta, and Waterville Street Railway. Augusta, GA., 127 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 826 v. San Diego Street Railway. San Diego., 128 (Reel 5)
  - Boiler Makers, Local 295 v. Stacy-Schmidt. York, PA., 129 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Maryland Pressed Steel. Hagerstown, MD., 130 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Nonnabo Chemical. Phillipsdale, RI, 131 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Fort Wayne and Northwestern Railway. Waterloo, IN., 132 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Conneaut Car. Conneaut, OH, 133 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Commonwealth Steel. Granite City, IL., 134 (Reel 5)
  - Gas Makers v. Minneapolis Gas Light. Minneapolis, MN., 135 (Reel 5)
  - Molders, Local 11 v. Rochester Foundrymen's Association. Rochester, NY., 136 (Reel 5)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 842 v. Wilmington and Philadelphia Traction. Wilmington, DE., 137 (Reel 5)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 65 and 122 v. Employers. Butte, MT., 138 (Reel 5)
  - Flour and Cereal Workers, Union 16302 v. Washburn Crosby et al. Minneapolis, MN., 139 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Cleveland Street Railway. Cleveland, OH., 140 (Reel 5)
  - Boiler Makers, Local 83 v. Kansas City Structural Steel. Kansas City and Argentine, KS., 141 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists, Local 459 v. Minnesota Manufacturing Association. St. Paul, MN., 142 (Reel 5)
  - Central Trades and Labor Assembly et al. v. New York Air Brake. Watertown, NY., 143 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists, Local 55 et al. v. Superior Tool and Die, et al. Columbus, OH., 144 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Spokane Inland Empire Railway. Spokane, WA., 145 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. Sloss-Sheffield Steel and iron. Florence, AL, 146 (Reel 5)
  - Engineers, Firemen, and Switchmen v. Garfield Smelting. Salt Lake City, UT, 147 (Reel 5)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. Planing Mills. Denver, 148 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. American Hide and Leather et al. Sheboygan, WI, 149 (Reel 5)
  - Machinists v. Goodyear Rubber et al. Akron, OH., 150 (Reel 5)
  - Employees v. S.B. Stine. Osceola Mills, PA., 151 (Reel 5)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. Carpenter Steel et al. Reading, PA., 152 (Reel 5)
  - Iron Workers, Local 10 v. Builders Association. Kansas City, MO, 153 (Reel 5)